<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>TBE Website </title>
    <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TBE Website </description>
    <image>
      <title>TBE Website </title>
      <url>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Leetcode Process</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/15/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/15/15/</guid>
      <description>From now on, I will post the interview questions I did here on leetcode and share important information about them here, such as important points I found important, parts I had difficulty with and new things I learned&amp;hellip;
👇You can find these questions on top at leetcode section👇
Leetcode </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Metaverse</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/14/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/14/14/</guid>
      <description>The Next Frontier in Digital Interaction👾 We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard of Metaverse lately, especially with the developments in VR headsets, everyone is interested in it. So what exactly is Metaverse? Metaverse is a virtual reality environment where users can communicate with each other. This is a computer generated environment and other participants in the long run will essentially act like a 3D version internet, even if it sounds a little different and unimaginative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Down Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/13/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/13/13/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Way More Than Just Crypto💰 We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard about Blockchain, right? Mostly in the same sentence with Bitcoin. But let me tell you, Blockchain is a whole universe beyond just cryptocurrency. I’ve spent some time diving into what blockchain really is and why it&amp;rsquo;s such an important. Here&amp;rsquo;s my opinion.
What&amp;rsquo;s Blockchain Anyway?💰 Consider blockchain to be a digital ledger. However, instead of being centrally managed it is distributed over thousands of computers globally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Navigating the World of Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/12/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/12/12/</guid>
      <description>Transforming How We Interact with Technology 🚩When we are first born as human beings we know almost nothing, but as the days go by we learn new things and apply them in our lives to build some skills. The same is true for machines, machine learning collects data and statistics from outside and starts to perform given tasks without programming. For example, if you show a computer a picture of a watermelon and an apple and it is programmed to learn, the statistical models in the data will allow it to recognize a watermelon or an apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Technology Behind Real-Time AI Interaction</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/11/eleventh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/11/eleventh/</guid>
      <description>🌌ChatGPT is really an amazing piece of AI technology that OpenAI has come up with. It&amp;rsquo;s like having a conversation with someone who understands and responds super quickly. What makes ChatGPT stand out is how well it gets what we&amp;rsquo;re saying and gives back responses that feel really human. It&amp;rsquo;s all thanks to some smart tech stuff called natural language processing (NLP) and machine learning. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to take you through how ChatGPT works, how it deals with the information we give it, and how it manages to reply so quickly and accurately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the World of Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/10/tenth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/10/tenth/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the Journey and Capabilities of AI 🔋In the ever-evolving landscape of technology, Artificial Intelligence (AI) emerges as a cornerstone of innovation and futuristic exploration. Originating from the realms of academic theory and science fiction, AI has made an extraordinary journey into the real world, becoming an integral part of our daily lives and a crucial component in various industries. This remarkable transition from concept to reality is fueled by advancements in computing power, data availability, and breakthroughs in machine learning algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding SaaS and Micro Saas</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/09/nineth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/09/nineth/</guid>
      <description>Redefining Software Delivery in the Modern Age:🛰️ Software as a Service (SaaS) is a cornerstone of current software delivery in the fast-paced world of technology. Micro SaaS, a minor but significant offshoot, is emerging from this sector. This post looks into the definitions of SaaS and Micro SaaS, as well as the trajectories of successful organizations in both fields.
Understanding Software as a Service (SaaS)🛰️ Software as a Service, or SaaS, is a software distribution model where applications are hosted by a service provider and made available to users over the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top-Paying Software Engineering Roles for Early Career Professionals</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/08/eight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/08/eight/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the Path to Prosperity🚀: Starting a career in software engineering provides up a plethora of profitable prospects. This article digs into the highest-paying job titles for early-career engineers, offering insight into the possible cash benefits and future opportunities in this dynamic sector.
Early Career High Earners: Top Software Engineering Roles: Front-End Engineer:🚀 Specializing in user interface design and user experience, these professionals ensure the usability and aesthetic appeal of applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chrome Extensions</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/07/seventh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/07/seventh/</guid>
      <description>Chrome extensions✅ are like to digital weapons for your web browser. They&amp;rsquo;re modest but powerful tools that allow you to shape and personalize your Google Chrome browsing experience. There&amp;rsquo;s a Chrome extension for everything, whether you want to boost your productivity, improve your online security, or simply make browsing more enjoyable. You may modify how you interact with webpages, streamline processes, and even add new functionality to your browser with these handy add-ons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Your Code on a Hugo Website</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/05/fifth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/05/fifth/</guid>
      <description>📌Incorporating code snippets into your Hugo website can greatly enhance its functionality and appeal, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re showcasing your programming projects. Markdown, a lightweight markup language, offers an easy way to format text and code for web pages. For example, in a Hugo site&amp;rsquo;s showcase section, you can display Java code neatly formatted for readability. Here&amp;rsquo;s how:
📌Open Your Markdown File: Navigate to the Markdown file where you want to include your code snippet in your Hugo site&amp;rsquo;s content folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Markdown</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/06/sixth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/06/sixth/</guid>
      <description>Markdown🌍 is a lightweight markup language that you can use to add formatting elements to plain text. The markdown syntax was created by John Gruber of Daring Fireball in 2004 to make text as readable as possible. Markdown is one of the most popular markup languages and has a loyal fanbase.
Markdown as a bridge between plain text and HTML
🌍There are several reasons for this strong devotion. The first is that Markdown has always been a power-user tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Deploy Website In Github</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/04/fourth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/04/fourth/</guid>
      <description>Deploying ⚙️ Creating a website on GitHub is an effective and professional way to present your projects and interests to a global audience. Utilizing GitHub Pages, you can host your site directly from a GitHub repository, offering a no-cost solution with the robust infrastructure of GitHub. This approach is not only economical but also integrates seamlessly with your development workflow.
⚙️By automating the deployment process, GitHub Actions offers another degree of efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github as a Hosting Platform</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/03/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/03/third/</guid>
      <description>❤️GitHub: The Premier Platform for Code Hosting and Collaboration 👉GitHub is generally acknowledged as a primary center for coding initiatives, with a focus on hosting, saving, and modifying code. GitHub, which is popular for source code management, provides powerful version control and collaboration tools. It is a popular platform for hosting tiny websites, project management, and team collaboration among both people and corporations. GitHub&amp;rsquo;s heart is in its &amp;ldquo;Repositories,&amp;rdquo; which are specialized locations for organizing code for specific projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I iteratively develop my website?</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/02/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/02/second/</guid>
      <description>To iteratively develop 🦾a Hugo static website and see changes on the spot, you can use Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in local server which live reloads as you make changes to your site. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide:
Install Hugo on your local machine. Navigate to your Hugo site directory via the command line. Run hugo server in the command line. This command starts a local web server and auto-regenerates your site whenever you make changes to the content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobbies</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about a range of hobbies that keep me balanced and engaged. Playing basketball is more than just a game for me; it&amp;rsquo;s a way to build teamwork skills and stay physically fit. When I&amp;rsquo;m not on the court, I love spending quality time with my friends, as it provides me with a strong support system and a break from my busy schedule. I&amp;rsquo;m also involved in club activities at my university, offering a structured way to pursue my interests and engage with my community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LeetCode</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/leetcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/leetcode/</guid>
      <description>I will post the interview questions I did here on leetcode and share important information about them here, such as important points I found important, parts I had difficulty with and new things I learned.
Remove Element Given an integer array nums and an integer val, remove all occurrences of val in nums in-place. The order of the elements may be changed. Then return the number of elements in nums which are not equal to val.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/resume/</guid>
      <description>SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS  Electrical and Computer engineering student specializing in Embedded Systems, Signal Conditioning, FPGA &amp;amp; PCB Design, Hardware Development and Project Management, with hands-on experience.  Applied programming skills with Java, C++, Python, HTML&amp;amp;CSS, and Git, firmware experience in FPGA &amp;amp; PCB projects  Eager to expand knowledge in Embedded Systems, Signal Conditioning and Digital Design to deliver effective projects.  Experience in research and project development, including designing a NASA-aligned meteor detection system at SEAL Lab and developing static websites to showcase educational resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Hugo?</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/01/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/01/first/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a popular, open-source static site generator that is used to build websites quickly and efficiently. Unlike systems that dynamically build a page with each visitor request, Hugo generates pages when you create or update your content. It converts your content into plain HTML files, providing reusable components and a convenient standard file structure​​​​​​.
A static website is one where the content is fixed and the same for every user, and is stored on the server as plain HTML files.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
