<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>TBE Website </title>
    <link>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TBE Website </description>
    <image>
      <title>TBE Website </title>
      <url>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Tugrul Baki Efesoy, a sophomore at the University of Washington pursuing dual majors in Computer Science and Electrical and Computer Engineering. In addition to my academic endeavors, I serve as the president of the Turkish Club, which boasts a vibrant community of over 50 active members. We focus on cultural events and educational initiatives to create an inclusive environment. Beyond academics and leadership, my hobbies like basketball and hiking provide a balanced lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobbies</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/hobbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/hobbies/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about a range of hobbies that keep me balanced and engaged. Playing basketball is more than just a game for me; it&amp;rsquo;s a way to build teamwork skills and stay physically fit. When I&amp;rsquo;m not on the court, I love spending quality time with my friends, as it provides me with a strong support system and a break from my busy schedule. I&amp;rsquo;m also involved in club activities at my university, offering a structured way to pursue my interests and engage with my community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I iteratively develop my website?</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/post/02/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/post/02/second/</guid>
      <description>To iteratively develop a Hugo static website and see changes on the spot, you can use Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in local server which live reloads as you make changes to your site. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide:
Install Hugo on your local machine. Navigate to your Hugo site directory via the command line. Run hugo server in the command line. This command starts a local web server and auto-regenerates your site whenever you make changes to the content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/showcase/</guid>
      <description>In this assessment, I have built a TODO list manager. Productivity tools like TODO lists are becoming increasingly popular and with File I/O and ArrayLists you will be able to build one (and implement one or more features of your choosing!). My TODO list manager will allow a user to add items to a TODO list, mark TODOs as completed and save and load TODOs to and from a file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Hugo?</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/post/01/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/deneme/post/01/first/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a popular open-source static site generator that is used to build websites quickly and efficiently. Unlike systems that dynamically build a page with each visitor request, Hugo generates pages when you create or update your content. It converts your content into plain HTML files, providing reusable components and a convenient standard file structure​​​​​​.
A static website is one where the content is fixed and the same for every user, and is stored on the server as plain HTML files.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
