<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on TBE Website </title>
    <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/categories/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on TBE Website </description>
    <image>
      <title>TBE Website </title>
      <url>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/categories/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Your Code on a Hugo Website</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/05/fifth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/05/fifth/</guid>
      <description>📌Incorporating code snippets into your Hugo website can greatly enhance its functionality and appeal, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re showcasing your programming projects. Markdown, a lightweight markup language, offers an easy way to format text and code for web pages. For example, in a Hugo site&amp;rsquo;s showcase section, you can display Java code neatly formatted for readability. Here&amp;rsquo;s how:
📌Open Your Markdown File: Navigate to the Markdown file where you want to include your code snippet in your Hugo site&amp;rsquo;s content folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I iteratively develop my website?</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/02/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/02/second/</guid>
      <description>To iteratively develop 🦾a Hugo static website and see changes on the spot, you can use Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in local server which live reloads as you make changes to your site. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide:
Install Hugo on your local machine. Navigate to your Hugo site directory via the command line. Run hugo server in the command line. This command starts a local web server and auto-regenerates your site whenever you make changes to the content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Hugo?</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/01/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/01/first/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a popular open-source static site generator that is used to build websites quickly and efficiently. Unlike systems that dynamically build a page with each visitor request, Hugo generates pages when you create or update your content. It converts your content into plain HTML files, providing reusable components and a convenient standard file structure​​​​​​.
A static website is one where the content is fixed and the same for every user, and is stored on the server as plain HTML files.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
