<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Engineering on TBE Website </title>
    <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/categories/software-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Engineering on TBE Website </description>
    <image>
      <title>TBE Website </title>
      <url>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/categories/software-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding SaaS and Micro Saas</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/09/nineth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/09/nineth/</guid>
      <description>Redefining Software Delivery in the Modern Age:🛰️ Software as a Service (SaaS) is a cornerstone of current software delivery in the fast-paced world of technology. Micro SaaS, a minor but significant offshoot, is emerging from this sector. This post looks into the definitions of SaaS and Micro SaaS, as well as the trajectories of successful organizations in both fields.
Understanding Software as a Service (SaaS)🛰️ Software as a Service, or SaaS, is a software distribution model where applications are hosted by a service provider and made available to users over the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top-Paying Software Engineering Roles for Early Career Professionals</title>
      <link>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/08/eight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbakie.github.io/TBEwebsite/post/08/eight/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the Path to Prosperity🚀: Starting a career in software engineering provides up a plethora of profitable prospects. This article digs into the highest-paying job titles for early-career engineers, offering insight into the possible cash benefits and future opportunities in this dynamic sector.
Early Career High Earners: Top Software Engineering Roles: Front-End Engineer:🚀 Specializing in user interface design and user experience, these professionals ensure the usability and aesthetic appeal of applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
